<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quickstart on Ensign Documentation</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Quickstart on Ensign Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Designing Event-Driven Architectures</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/edas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:51:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/edas/</guid><description>An event-driven architecture (EDA) is a plan for how data will flow through your application. It can be helpful to decompose these architectures into different handlers that are responsible for performing operations on the data (e.g. ingestion, statistical inference, prediction) and routing it between the layers of your application via the topics.
Handlers usually fall into two categories, &amp;ldquo;Publishers&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Subscribers&amp;rdquo;. Publishers are responsible for writing data to topics, while consumers read data from those topics and perform some transformation on it (e.</description></item><item><title>Naming Topics</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/topics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 11:17:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/getting-started/topics/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s the best way to name your topics? This is an excellent question!
Remember, a topic is just like a table in a traditional relational database, so it can be helpful to think about that as you name them.
Each team may have slightly different naming conventions, and the most important thing when it comes to naming is that your teammates understand the names you use!
That said, our favorite technique is to give each data source and type its own topic, for instance:</description></item></channel></rss>