<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>End-to-End Examples on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/</link><description>Recent content in End-to-End Examples on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ensign for Application Developers</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/developers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/developers/</guid><description>Hi there! This tutorial is targeted towards Golang application developers. If you are interested in or currently writing event-driven applications in Go you are in the right place! In this code-driven tutorial we will use the Ensign Golang SDK to publish curated tweets to an event stream and retrieve them in real time.
If you came here for the code the full example is available here .
Prerequisites To follow along with this tutorial you&amp;rsquo;ll need to:</description></item><item><title>Ensign for Data Engineers</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/data_engineers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/data_engineers/</guid><description>We love data engineers — it&amp;rsquo;s how a lot of us got our starts in tech. One of the main reasons we made Ensign is to make it easier for you to put your data in motion. We know that a clumsy ETL routine can quickly turn a data lake into a data landfill.
In this example we&amp;rsquo;ll see how to move data around with Ensign. We&amp;rsquo;ll be using Watermill-Ensign and Watermill to call a Weather API and insert weather data into a PostgreSQL database.</description></item><item><title>Ensign for Data Scientists</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/data_scientists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/examples/data_scientists/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a question we frequently get from our data scientist friends:
What does event-driven data science even look like??
In this tutorial we&amp;rsquo;ll find out! Join along in implementing an event-driven Natural Language Processing tool that does streaming HTML parsing, entity extraction, and sentiment analysis.
Just here for the code? Check it out here !
Prerequisites To follow along with this tutorial you&amp;rsquo;ll need to:
Generate an API key to access Ensign Set up your GOPATH and workspace Create an Ensign client Back to the Future Did you know?</description></item></channel></rss>