<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ensign Internals on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/</link><description>Recent content in Ensign Internals on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/configuration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/configuration/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Note: This page is for internal Ensign development and will probably not be very useful to Ensign users.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ensign services are primarily configured using environment variables and will respect &lt;a href="https://github.com/joho/godotenv"
target="_blank"
>dotenv files&lt;/a>
in the current working directory. The canonical reference of the configuration for an Ensign service is the &lt;code>config&lt;/code> package of that service (described below). This documentation enumerates the most important configuration variables, their default values, and any hints or warnings about how to use them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Required Configuration&lt;/strong>&lt;br />
If a configuration parameter does not have a default value that means it is required and must be specified by the user! If the configuration parameter does have a default value then that environment variable does not have to be set.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Staging</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/staging/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/system/staging/</guid><description>Note: This page is for internal Ensign development and will probably not be very useful to Ensign users. The staging environment has the latest code deployed frequently, may introduce breaking changes, and has it&amp;rsquo;s data routinely deleted.
Staging Environment Ensign developers can access the staging environment in order to perform testing and development or to QA release candidates before they are deployed.
To get started, make sure that you&amp;rsquo;ve created an API Key in the staging environment using the Beacon UI at https://ensign.</description></item></channel></rss>