<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eventing 101 on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/</link><description>Recent content in Eventing 101 on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:01:45 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/use_cases/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/use_cases/</guid><description>Oh, The Places You’ll Go! with Ensign 😉
Ensign is an eventing platform for developers that dramatically simplifies real-time apps and analytics. Here’s a list of ideas we dreamed up that are possible to build on Ensign. We grouped them by use case, but it&amp;rsquo;s by no means exhaustive. We hope it gets your creative wheels turning!
Civic Engagement Active First Responders Real-Time Civic Notices Digital Democracy Moderator-less Message Boards Anti-Human Trafficking Tools Climate Change Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) Dashboard Climate Change Monitor Carbon Credit Exchange Weather Change Monitors Customer Experience Live Customer Support &amp;amp; On-Call Management In-Store IoT for Point of Sale (e.</description></item><item><title>Data Sources</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/data_sources/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/data_sources/</guid><description>Looking for inspiration? Check out some of these public streaming data sources!
Realtime Source Data API Type SDKs Account Required Limits Finnhub Stock prices, company profiles, company &amp;amp; market news REST, Web Socket Go SDK Yes Unknown CoinCap Cryptocurrency prices across exchanges REST, Web Socket N/A No 200 requests/min Flight Data Vehicle and flight locations Open REST API Python API No 4000 daily credits DC WMATA Bus &amp;amp; train trip updates, alerts, and vehicle positions GTFS protocol buffers N/A Yes No Weather API Weather data REST Python, Go Yes No USGS Earthquake Data Earthquake data (time, location, etc) REST API No No No</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/glossary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/glossary/</guid><description>When you&amp;rsquo;re learning a new technology, there always a LOT of new lingo. We&amp;rsquo;ve tried to gather them all together here to help get you started:
api key &amp;ldquo;API&amp;rdquo; stands for &amp;ldquo;Application Programming Interface&amp;rdquo;, which is a very broad term that refers (super high level) to the ways in which users or other applications can interact with an application.
Some applications (like Ensign) require permission to interact with, such as a password, token, or key.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/faq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/eventing/faq/</guid><description>Got a question you don&amp;rsquo;t see here? Let us know so we can add it! support@rotational.io What is an event (or data) stream? You can think of an event stream as a pipeline through which data flows, much like pipes that move water in your home. You can use an event stream to connect data sources that produce or emit data (events) to data sinks that consume or process the data.</description></item></channel></rss>