<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer SDKs on Ensign Documentation</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/</link><description>Recent content in Developer SDKs on Ensign Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/python/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/python/</guid><description>The Python SDK is the quickest way to get started with Ensign. In this example we&amp;rsquo;ll create a simple Python project from scratch to publish and subscribe to Ensign!
Prerequisites create a free Ensign account and API key download and install Python according to your operating system The Python SDK is currently compatible with Python 3.7, 3.8, 3.9, and 3.10.
Project Setup Create a project directory and install the official Python SDK using pip.</description></item><item><title>Golang</title><link>https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/golang/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:03:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ensign.rotational.dev/sdk/golang/</guid><description>The Go SDK is a great choice for developers who wish to integrate Ensign into their existing projects. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re starting from scratch and want to take advantage of Golang&amp;rsquo;s static typing and high-performance multiprocessing, that&amp;rsquo;s cool too.
In this example we&amp;rsquo;ll create a simple Go project from scratch to publish and subscribe to Ensign!
Prerequisites create a free Ensign account and API key download and install Golang according to your operating system Project Setup As with any new Go project, start by creating a directory and module to start adding dependencies to.</description></item></channel></rss>